six years ago in October this year
October be six years I was diagnosed
with colon cancer I had the cancer
removed six year will be my six year
anniversary in October ever being done
with it I had I had to lose the weight
at six years ago I was about three
hundred three hundred and forty three
pounds oh crap I was three hundred three
hundred forty three pounds now I'm at
270 274 273 pounds trying to get down
trying to get it out and I'm telling you
some fellas we need to be more aware we
do we need to be more aware of our I
know a lot of guys think they Superman
that's what I like to do when I do my
shows I like to talk to the fellas and
be like you know what we need to get our
awareness up cuz I'll give you all a
real number seven out of ten guys
seventy percent of guys will die for me
the prostate colon or testicular cancer
that's real seventy percent of us cause
we don't have no awareness we don't say
that we keep it here with Superman we're
not to say nothing I know most men will
stand in a crooked position cuz
something hurts just in us you know what
I'm talking about you gotta work DC
field field standing like this you won't
pass city like Co what's wrong
no need to go away leave me alone
and fellas do we help feel no we don't
help feel we make fun of Phil the whole
night at the top we see Phil hey Phil we
need to stop Phil needs to see a doctor
fellas we need to be aware we need to be
we need to get our awareness up like the
ladies ladies your awareness is
fantastic fantastic if there's something
wrong in the female world you will let
everybody know you will stop people you
know today is but that's good that's
fantastic you would never let your best
friend stand there crooked your best
friend you that girl what's wrong with
you what's this straighten yourself up
that's what we need to do fellas we need
to be like that don't go through what I
went through don't wait till the last
minute before you got to go see your dad
it's time you're gonna see your doctor
go see your doctor don't go through they
get a lot of stuff back here they did
but I'm glad they got it out I'm glad it
was done I'm after all my surgeries
after everything was done after all of
that my recovery I have a new respect
for you ladies now I do cuz I had to be
off a little bit for real when I was
going through my recovery from this from
the surgeries I was still alone I was
still bleeding in the back side so I had
to wear maxi pads
for about two weeks it's not funny I
didn't even know they had a sticky side
I didn't know how they work mine just
moved around every time I walk I walk
around like no this is not right this is
not right this is why they always mad no
I get it now I had to call my sister I
was like how did you keep these things
still she was like it you feel it I
liked it I feel what she was like that
little piece of paper what did you think
that was I thought it was an air
freshener I don't know what she was like
no you idiot you peel it stick it then
you're good so I did and it was
fantastic after that I was like okay
there it is there it is I was give a
random ladies high-five
subscribe to drive our comedy for even
more of the world's largest collection
of clean comedy